<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Riddle Me This!</string>
    <string name="desc">image</string>
    <string name="creator">by Akshay Sathiya</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="level1">Level 1</string>
    <string name="lvl1txt">I run for miles and miles, but I never actually move. What am I?</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer:</string>
    <string name="test">GUESS!</string>
    <string name="level2">Level 2</string>
    <string name="lvl2txt"> I am very slow. I only have a foot, no legs. What am I?</string>
    <string name="lvl3txt">I am brown, have a head and a tail, but no legs or arms. What am I?</string>
    <string name="level3">Level 3</string>
    <string name="congrats">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="endmessage">You have successfully solved every riddle in Riddle Me This! Check out Riddle Me This! on the Google Play Store soon for new updates and riddles!</string>
    <string name="copyright">© 2017 Akshay Sathiya All Rights Reserved</string>
    <string name="lvl4txt">I have four eyes, but I cannot see. What am I?</string>
    <string name="level4">Level 4</string>
    <string name="level5">Level 5</string>
    <string name="lvl5txt">The more I am taken, the more I leave behind. What am I?</string>
    <string name="level6">Level 6</string>
    <string name="lvl6txt">Some nights you may see all of me, some you may only see a part of me, and some you may not see me at all. What am I?</string>
    <string name="level7">Level 7</string>
    <string name="lvl7txt">I travel around the world, but I am always in the same place, what am I?</string>
    <string name="level8">Level 8</string>
    <string name="lvl8txt">If I have it, I don\'t share it. If I share it, I don\'t have it. What is it?</string>
    <string name="level9">Level 9</string>
    <string name="lvl9txt">What is so delicate that merely saying its name breaks it?</string>
    <string name="modeselect">Select Mode</string>
    <string name="freestyle">Freestyle</string>
    <string name="timetrial">Time Trial</string>
    <string name="survival">Survival</string>
    <string name="howtoplay">How to Play</string>
    <string name="workinprog">This feature is a work in progress! Check out the Google Play Store soon!</string>
    <string name="desc_freestyle">Answer as many riddles as you can, without any constraints such as a set number of lives or a time limit. Open up the frontier of riddles as large as you can imagine, with unlimited lives, unlimited time, and unlimited fun!</string>
    <string name="desc_timetrial">Answer as many riddles as you can before time runs out! You only have 10 seconds for each riddle! In order to beat the clock, solve these riddles as fast as you can! Are you up to the challenge?</string>
    <string name="desc_survival">Answer as many riddles as you can, but be careful! Every wrong guess is a lost life! This is no game of speed, but it is a game of patience and critical thinking. You start with 3 lives, and a long trail of riddles lies ahead of you. Can you make the trek?</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="playagain">Play Again!</string>
    <string name="Time">Time:</string>
    <string name="gameover">GAME OVER</string>
    <string name="gameovermsg">Aw! You lost! Ready to give it another go?</string>
    <string name="blank" />
    <string name="play">PLAY</string>
    <string name="newdesc">Answer as many riddles as you can! You have an entire road of riddles ahead of you, and you are equipped with the most powerful weapons anyone can have: knowledge and wisdom. Are you ready to make the trek?</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits1">This app, Riddle Me This!, was created by Akshay Sathiya, in 2017. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="riddlecourtesy">Most of the riddles featured in this app are from the following websites:</string>
    <string name="url1">https://www.riddles.com/best-riddles</string>
    <string name="url2">http://www.funology.com/riddles/</string>
    <string name="gameovermessage">Oh no! You lost all of your lives! But this is not the end! Try, try again!</string>
    <string name="level10">Level 10</string>
    <string name="lvl10txt">What type of tree can you hold in your hand?</string>
    <string name="level11">Level 11</string>
    <string name="lvl11txt">What is the center of gravity?</string>
    <string name="level12">Level 12</string>
    <string name="lvl12txt">Which eight-letter word still remains a word as you remove each letter from it, one by one?</string>
    <string name="piccredits">Most of the images/pictures featured in this app are from Google Images.</string>
</resources>
